export const dataSet = [
  {
    video: (
      <div className="player-container">
        <iframe
          width="auto"
          height="auto"
          src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/k4MPJKp8vGg"
          frameBorder="0"
          allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
          allowFullScreen
        />
      </div>
    ),
    question: "What is 8 x 1?",
    answers: ["1", "8", "16", "9"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    video: (
      <div className="player-container">
        <iframe
          width="auto"
          height="auto"
          src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8NeNRk-v780"
          frameborder="0"
          allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
          allowfullscreen
        />
      </div>
    ),
    question: "Who is Steve Jobs?",
    answers: ["CEO of Microsoft", "Barber in NY", "Movie Star", "CEO of Apple"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Metallica is a ____ band",
    answers: ["Blues", "Hard-Rock", "Jazz", "Metal"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "IS is a ____",
    answers: ["Word", "Band", "Terror Group", "Brand"],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who was Einstein",
    answers: [
      "A Scientist",
      "A Dentist",
      "A Serial Killer",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "JavaScript can be used in ____ development",
    answers: ["Back-End", "Front-End", "ReactJS", "All of the Above"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Hitler was a",
    answers: [
      "Mass Murderer",
      "Dictator",
      "Jew",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correct: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Korn is a",
    answers: ["Nu-Metal band", "Religion", "Singer"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Windows computers are",
    answers: ["Horrible", "Great", "Cheap", "Invented by Bill Gates"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "The BigBan stands in",
    answers: ["Egypt", "London", "Amsterdam", "NewYork"],
    correct: 1
  }
];

export const dataSet2 = [
  {
    video: (
      <div className="player-container">
        <iframe
          width="auto"
          height="auto"
          src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_S8gf4S-1iI"
          frameBorder="0"
          allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
          allowFullScreen
        />
      </div>
    ),
    question: "What is the answer to the question2?",
    answers: ["this", "that", "the other", "none of the above!"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    video: (
      <div className="player-container">
        <iframe
          width="auto"
          height="auto"
          src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/D7aYjRl_6Zw"
          frameborder="0"
          allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
          allowfullscreen
        />
      </div>
    ),
    question: "Who is Steve Jobs?",
    answers: ["CEO of Microsoft", "Barber in NY", "Movie Star", "CEO of Apple"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Metallica is a ____ band",
    answers: ["Blues", "Hard-Rock", "Jazz", "Metal"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "IS is a ____",
    answers: ["Word", "Band", "Terror Group", "Brand"],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who was Einstein",
    answers: [
      "A Scientist",
      "A Dentist",
      "A Serial Killer",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "JavaScript can be used in ____ development",
    answers: ["Back-End", "Front-End", "ReactJS", "All of the Above"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Hitler was a",
    answers: [
      "Mass Murderer",
      "Dictator",
      "Jew",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correct: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Korn is a",
    answers: ["Nu-Metal band", "Religion", "Singer"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Windows computers are",
    answers: ["Horrible", "Great", "Cheap", "Invented by Bill Gates"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "The BigBan stands in",
    answers: ["Egypt", "London", "Amsterdam", "NewYork"],
    correct: 1
  }
];

export const dataSet3 = [
  {
    video: (
      <div className="player-container">
        <iframe
          width="auto"
          height="auto"
          src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_S8gf4S-1iI"
          frameBorder="0"
          allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
          allowFullScreen
        />
      </div>
    ),
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the answer to the question3?",
    answers: ["this", "that", "the other", "none of the above!"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    video: (
      <div className="player-container">
        <iframe
          width="auto"
          height="auto"
          src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/D7aYjRl_6Zw"
          frameborder="0"
          allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"
          allowfullscreen
        />
      </div>
    ),
    id: 2,
    question: "Who is Steve Jobs?",
    answers: ["CEO of Microsoft", "Barber in NY", "Movie Star", "CEO of Apple"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Metallica is a ____ band",
    answers: ["Blues", "Hard-Rock", "Jazz", "Metal"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "IS is a ____",
    answers: ["Word", "Band", "Terror Group", "Brand"],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who was Einstein",
    answers: [
      "A Scientist",
      "A Dentist",
      "A Serial Killer",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "JavaScript can be used in ____ development",
    answers: ["Back-End", "Front-End", "ReactJS", "All of the Above"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Hitler was a",
    answers: [
      "Mass Murderer",
      "Dictator",
      "Jew",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correct: 4
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Korn is a",
    answers: ["Nu-Metal band", "Religion", "Singer"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Windows computers are",
    answers: ["Horrible", "Great", "Cheap", "Invented by Bill Gates"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "The BigBan stands in",
    answers: ["Egypt", "London", "Amsterdam", "NewYork"],
    correct: 1
  }
];
